A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
I'm gonna cut you into ribbons, double-speed soul legs!
You don't get it, do you?
Your attacks follow the exact same rhythm as that music you're listening to.
I know every move you're gonna make. Why not take the headphones out?
I'm afraid you're wrong.
Which isn't surprising.
Your thought process is so simplistic I don't have to listen to know what you're saying.
Your thoughts are written all over your face.
You just want me to take out the headphones so you can have them, don't you?
That's right!
Triple-speed soul legs!
Total Destruction Current!
Strike!
Now it's my turn, law-abiding!
Silver Gun!
Damn, went back, priest!
I can't go much longer in this condition.
How long are you going to lay there in the snow?
I'm not ready to bury you yet.
I'm waiting.
A snowman decoy?
Oh, yes, I remember. He's a puppeteer.
These are nothing but cheap knock-offs.
Disappointing.
He turned tail and ran again.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
He's a husband...
I'm helping my body.
He's one who is dreaming.
I'm falling down at my eyes.
I'm gonna stay wild.
I'm falling down to my eyes.
…
I'll see you in your dreams, yeah, baby.
I'll see you in your dreams, baby.
Misenay sisters, welcome back.
How did it go?
Unleash the Seven's resonance, Link.
A recital of destruction and creation?
Play.
Play, soul.
Now's your chance to open your eyes to what you can become.
You think you're already cool?
You don't know what cool is.
Not yet.
Can't you feel it calling you?
Play.
Stop doubting. Stop hesitating.
It's time to start living.
What are you waiting for, you coward?
At this rate, your soul is going to waste away.
It's just sitting there, doing nothing, stagnating.
That isn't cool, soul.
You're better than this and you know it.
Come on.
Let's have some fun.
Aren't you tired of remaining calm, collected, cold?
Don't you want more than that?
Life's not meant to be a boring series of events one day simply following the next.
Play it.
Play.
Revel in the sound.
Play it now, soul.
It's time.
Play.
Are you listening?
Play!
So, how?
I can feel our wavelengths starting to combine.
Here we go.
Play it, Link.
Die.
Damn you.
We got him now.
We've got him now.
Nice try.
Concentrate on his left.
What is this?
Their attack's completely different from before.
Arh...
elevate the sword.
Sold.
Spets.
J intensely.
How are they moving so fast?
I can't keep up with them.
These brats are stronger than I expected.
I was at the height of my strength in this body, and I'm losing.
It's your turn, Blackstar.
Tsubaki, get ready for Soul Resonance.
Soul's piano playing is raising our resonance rate exponentially.
If this keeps up while we're in Enchanted Sword mode, it could be dangerous.
He's attacking with shadows.
All right, reel him in!
Shadow Star. Checkmate Slash.
How'd you like that?
Tsubaki, release Enchanted Sword mode.
Okay.
How dare you!
You're up, kid.
Resonance stable.
Noise at 2.4%.
Black Needle Soul wavelength, fully charged.
It looks like you've got some scratches on that shiny steel body of yours.
Feedback in five seconds.
Four, three, two, one.
Dead cannon.
Windows penalties.
Maka.
I can hear it, so clearly.
The sound of his soul, all his emotions, they're flowing from him straight into me.
What I'm sensing is...
Faith and confidence.
This is our foundation.
This is our courage.
Soul Resonance!
What a strong soul! Incredible!
Impossible. That technique's too advanced for a child.
Let's go!
I've never seen that attack.
Is it Witch Hunter? No, it isn't. It's much more powerful than that. Genie Hunter!
Genie Hunter!
Ah!
Game quiet!
I've never seen that attack.
Is it Witch Hunter?
No, it isn't.
It's much more powerful than that.
Genie Hunter!
Help!
I don't know. It seems like overkill.
Where's his hat? And the magic tool?
Sorry. I don't know.
No. There was nothing you could do, Marka.
Sneaky old man. He was able to get away from us.
He detached his head from his body and took off.
All right, then we go after him. He can't have gone far.
No, we can't. The song is over now.
Our time's up.
No, it isn't up yet. We've got a few minutes.
Think about it.
Before the old dude changed his body, he was debating which form to take.
The one from 400 years back or from 100.
He'll just change his body again if we catch him.
Sol's right.
If he can keep transforming to avoid the field's effects, he'll easily outlast us.
Let's withdraw. We have no other choice at this point.
Come on. Let's go.
I recovered the magic tool.
I successfully completed the assigned mission.
So why do I feel like I was the one defeated back there?
How humiliating.
Me reduced to this.
Those brats will pay, I swear it.
Maka!
Black Star!
Where are you?
Looks like you're all in one piece.
Hurry, you guys. The time is almost up.
This way.
I thought you were still outside.
What are you doing here?
What's with the panting, Black Star?
That's not like you at all.
Shut up.
Just give me a hand, will ya?
Sure.
That's why we came in the first place.
Hm.
What? What the hell is that?
Not good.
No, we're goners for sure.
We're all gonna die.
Goodbye, too.
This is just an image of what happened 800 years ago.
We'll be fine.
We're just seeing a blast that went off back then.
I knew this wasn't good!
We're gonna die!
Uh, guys, it isn't real.
Oh, hey, I guess you're right.
How about that?
Eibon.
Let's get out of here.
We failed, I'm sorry.
The enemy got through.
Uh, Miss Marie?
Oh, if you were in big trouble once we get back to the Academy,
you should prepare yourselves.
Hey!
Why am I the only one you've got by the neck?
I'm so glad you're okay.
Hey, over here.
Don't worry, Sid.
It's fine.
We're all right.
You had us all terrified.
And what about Brew?
Is it ours?
Oh, I see.
Stein, can you stand up?
Here, let me help you.
Thank you.
Marka!
What's this, Amir?
Once we're off the island,
I want you to use it to give Lord Death a full report of what happened here.
Can you handle that?
Yes, sir.
Well, it's over.
Let's go home.
Forty-two, forty-two, five-sixty-four.
Hello, Lord Death.
Are you there?
My Marka!
Are you okay?
I was so, so, so, so, so worried about you.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Calm down.
Can you put Lord Death on?
Hello, hello.
What's up, what's up, what's up?
Good to see you.
So, how'd the mission go?
You see, sir.
Oh, well, I'm sure you did all you could.
I have returned, Lady Arachne.
So I see, Mosquito.
And was the mission successful?
Have you brought Brew to me as well?
Come.
I would like to look at it.
Yes, ma'am.
Here it is.
Is something wrong?
Take it out of its case.
Well, my lady.
I fear 800 years was too long for it to be inside that field.
What are you saying, Mosquito?
The device has been degraded.
Brew is worthless.
It no longer functions.
Is that so?
Fortunately, I always prepared for the worst.
Look at me, Mosquito.
My lady, I'm sorry.
Our 800 years of suffering were all for nothing.
Functional or not, I'm now in possession of Brew.
That's enough to frighten our enemies.
After all, the DWMA doesn't know that Brew is broken.
Yes, indeed.
What a truly delicious bluff, the lady.
The information that Arachnophobia possesses the tool is a weapon in its own right.
And I happen to excel at spreading such information.
We have acquired Brew, the most powerful tool created by the Great Wizard.
We are armed with a threat and our enemy's fear.
Well done.
Now, where is it?
Right here.
This is the real version of Brew.
Arachne, what a silly little fool.
She caused that explosion all those centuries ago to keep Brew's existence hidden from the Reaper.
Your spies did very well, Erika.
Thanks to them, we knew it had survived the blast.
Arachne didn't think to plant any surveillance spiders in the magnetic field.
That made it a simple enough task for us to swipe the real Brew and leave behind the useless fake we had created to use as a decoy.
And Arachne will have no idea the magic tool in her possession isn't even the real thing.
The problem now is the DWMA, right?
How do we keep them out of the way?
I still have Krona spying on them for me.
Have you forgotten?
You helped him plant that bug, right?
No, of course I remember!
Krona and I planted that snake inside Professor Stein's partner.
You understand that that little snake is more than just a way of listening in on their conversations, don't you?
Kinda.
That snake was implanted with a magic designed to speed up his madness.
It's not my best work, but it should be enough.
Stein's mental state isn't the most stable to begin with.
But it's a balancing act.
We don't want his madness to reach its peak too soon or too late.
The Reaper places great faith in Stein.
He'll be sent to the forefront of the battle.
While fighting, Stein will naturally have to resonate with his partner.
And when he does, the snake's magic will hit him all at once.
She knew there was going to be a struggle of R'Groo before she placed that snake.
She's controlling this huge fight between the two sides with one tiny reptile?
R'Groo, the Tempest.
Only someone who knows how to create a truly great storm deserves it.
This is just the beginning for the Academy and Arachnophobia.
And you,
Kishin.
R'Groo, the Tempest.
R'Qu Sword
Thank you.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the detective's first case, Kid exposes the DWMA's secret?
Symmetry is perfection.